export const data = {
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How would you describe your thoughts when facing challenges or distressing situations?",
            "options": [
                "Calm and composed+0",
                "Occasionally uneasy+1",
                "Frequently consider healthier coping strategies+2",
                "Consistently seeking healthier ways to cope+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Consistently seeking healthier ways to cope"
        },
        {
            "question": "How often do you find yourself contemplating self-harm as a coping mechanism?",
            "options": [
                "Rarely or never+0",
                "Occasionally+1",
                "Frequently, but actively seeking alternatives+2",
                "Regularly, but actively seeking alternatives and professional support+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Regularly, but actively seeking alternatives and professional support"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you often feel overwhelmed by emotions that drive you towards self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "Never+0",
                "Rarely+1",
                "Sometimes, but I'm actively working on managing them+2",
                "Frequently, but I'm actively seeking support and coping strategies+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Sometimes, but I'm actively working on managing them"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long do episodes of considering or engaging in self-harm typically last?",
            "options": [
                "A few minutes+0",
                "Several minutes+1",
                "Half an hour or more, but actively seeking alternatives+2",
                "Varies, but actively seeking alternatives and professional support+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "A few minutes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with self-harm or self-injury issues?",
            "options": [
                "Yes+0",
                "Considering it+1",
                "No, not yet, but actively considering seeking support+2",
                "No, and I don't plan to+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Considering it"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do these experiences of self-harm impact your daily life, relationships, or activities?",
            "options": [
                "Low impact+0",
                "Moderate impact, but actively working on reducing it+1",
                "High impact, but seeking support and coping strategies+2",
                "Very high impact, actively seeking professional help and support+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "High impact, but seeking support and coping strategies"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have others expressed concern about your experiences of persistent thoughts of self-harm or self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "Never+0",
                "Rarely+1",
                "Sometimes, but I'm open about my efforts to improve+2",
                "Frequently, and I appreciate their support as I work on improving+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Sometimes, but I'm open about my efforts to improve"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing self-harming behaviors is important for overall well-being?",
            "options": [
                "Strongly agree+0",
                "Agree, and actively taking steps to address it+1",
                "Neutral, but open to exploring ways to improve+2",
                "Disagree+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Agree, and actively taking steps to address it"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you been experiencing persistent thoughts of self-harm or engaging in self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "A short period+0",
                "Several months+1",
                "Years, but actively seeking support and making progress+2",
                "I haven't experienced persistent thoughts of self-harm or engaged in self-harming behaviors+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Years, but actively seeking support and making progress"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you noticed changes in your sleeping patterns, such as difficulty falling asleep, staying asleep, or experiencing excessive sleepiness?",
            "options": [
                "Occasionally+0",
                "Frequently, but taking steps to improve my sleep hygiene+1",
                "Consistently, actively seeking strategies to enhance my sleep quality+2",
                "I haven't noticed any changes in my sleeping patterns+3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Consistently"
        }
    ]
}
